const data = [
    {
        "question": "What is the Australian system of government?",
        "options": [
            "Presidential democracy",
            "Constitutional monarchy",
            "Parliamentary democracy",
            "Absolute monarchy"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Parliamentary democracy",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does 'Compulsory voting' mean in Australia?",
        "options": [
            "Voting is optional",
            "Voting is required by law",
            "Voting is restricted to certain individuals",
            "Voting is based on a lottery system"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Voting is required by law",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the foundation of Australia's legal system?",
        "options": [
            "Religious laws",
            "Australian Constitution",
            "Cultural practices",
            "Foreign legal systems"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Australian Constitution",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "Under the Rule of Law, who is equal in relation to the law?",
        "options": [
            "Only citizens",
            "Politicians",
            "Everyone",
            "Police officers"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Everyone",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of democracy does Australia have?",
        "options": [
            "Direct democracy",
            "Representative democracy",
            "Authoritarian democracy",
            "Monarchical democracy"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Representative democracy",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does 'Freedom of speech' mean in Australia?",
        "options": [
            "Unrestricted speech",
            "Speech with government approval",
            "Speech promoting violence",
            "Speech within the law"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Speech within the law",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 'Freedom of association' in Australia?",
        "options": [
            "Forced association",
            "Freedom to remain isolated",
            "Freedom to join or leave groups within the law",
            "Freedom to associate only with like-minded individuals"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Freedom to join or leave groups within the law",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there an official national religion in Australia?",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No",
            "It varies by region",
            "Only for citizens"
        ],
        "correct_option": "No",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does 'Equality of all people under the law' mean?",
        "options": [
            "Preferential treatment for certain groups",
            "Equal rights for all, regardless of differences",
            "Exclusion of certain groups from legal protection",
            "Selective application of laws"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Equal rights for all, regardless of differences",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the principle of 'A fair go' emphasize?",
        "options": [
            "Equal outcomes for all",
            "Class distinctions",
            "Equal opportunities for everyone",
            "Limitations based on background"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Equal opportunities for everyone",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 'Mutual respect and tolerance for others' based on?",
        "options": [
            "Agreement on all issues",
            "Violence and intimidation",
            "Freedom to insult others",
            "Respect for opinions and choices"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Respect for opinions and choices",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the value of 'Making a contribution' in Australian society?",
        "options": [
            "Isolation from the community",
            "Active participation and support for oneself and others",
            "Dependency on others",
            "Exemption from responsibilities"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Active participation and support for oneself and others",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does 'Compassion for those in need' involve?",
        "options": [
            "Ignoring those in need",
            "Helping others in times of need",
            "Promoting dependency",
            "Selective assistance based on criteria"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Helping others in times of need",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is the English language valued in Australia?",
        "options": [
            "Exclusion of non-English speakers",
            "Nationalism",
            "Economic participation and social cohesion",
            "Cultural superiority"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Economic participation and social cohesion",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What responsibilities do Australians have to protect society?",
        "options": [
            "Ignore suspicious activities",
            "Help protect society from crime and abuse",
            "Promote criminal activities",
            "Participate in illegal activities"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Help protect society from crime and abuse",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is online abuse accepted in Australia?",
        "options": [
            "Yes, if it's anonymous",
            "Yes, if it's against specific individuals",
            "No, it is not accepted",
            "It depends on the content"
        ],
        "correct_option": "No, it is not accepted",
        "topic": "values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does 'Loyalty to Australia' mean for citizens?",
        "options": [
            "Exclusive loyalty to Australia",
            "Loyalty to any country except Australia",
            "Loyalty to Australia and its people, even with dual citizenship",
            "Loyalty to the government, not the people"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Loyalty to Australia and its people, even with dual citizenship"
    }
]

export default data;